Do you know what time it is?
Can't sleep.
There are tabs for that.
Yeah. but then I'd be sleeping.
Dreams again.
Want to fight?
- I slipped.
- Right. You slipped.
As a result of me punching
you in the face.
I was already slipping when you
happened to punch me in the face.
But you most probably did.
Tell me about this dream.
Anything new?
No.
You have to let go of the past.
Can't remember my past.
It's causing you doubt. And
doubt makes you vulnerable.
Control it.
Learn to control again. You'll have to
commune with the Supreme Intelligence.
There's nothing more dangerous
to a warrior than emotion.
Humor is a distraction.
Anger... anger
represents the enemy.
120 days since the
last Skrull attack.
Has anyone ever seen what the Supreme
Intelligence really looks like?
No one can look upon the Supreme
Intelligence in its true form.
You know that.
Our subconcious chooses the way
they appear to us. so it's sacred.
It's personal.
No Kree divulges it. Ever.
Who do you see?
- Your brother.
- No.
- Father.
- Your old commander.
- Vers.
It's me you see. isn't it?
I see what you're trying to do.
- Is it working?
- Yes.
But you won't succeed
in changing the subject.
What is the point of giving me these
if you don't want me to use them?
I want you to use them.
The Supreme Intelligence gave me
responsibility of showing you how to use them.
I know how.
Well if that were true. you could've
knocked me down without it.
Control your impulses.
Stop using this. and
start using this.
I want you...
to be the best
version of yourself.
Vers.
Intelligence.
Your commander insists
that you're fit to serve.
I am.
You struggle with your emotions.
With your past. what fuels them.
You are just one victim of the
Skrull expansion that has
threatened our civilization for centuries.
Imposters who silently infiltrate.
then take over our planets.
Horrors that you remember.
and so much that you do not.
It's all blank...
My life.
You're supposed to take the
form of who I used to admire.
but I don't even remember
who this person was to me.
Perhaps. this is a mercy.
Sparing you from a deeper pain.
Freeing you to do
what all Kree must.
Put your people's needs
before your own.
We've given you a great gift.
The chance to fight for
the good of all Kree.
I want to serve.
Then master yourself.
What was given can
be taken away.
I won't let you down.
We'll know soon enough.
You have a mission.
Serve well and with honor.
This can't be good.
Must be another Skrull attack.
Whatever it is. it's big.
- Has a Skrull ever simmed you?
- Once.
- It was deeeply disturbing.
- Why?
Because I stared into the
face of my mortal enemy
and the face staring back
was my own.
Maybe if you were more attractive.
then it would be less disturbing.
You think you're funny.
I'm not laughing.
- You never laugh.
- I laugh. On the inside.
I'm not doing it now.
It's funny. 'cause objectively
speaking. you're quite handsome.
Well. thank you.
Listen up. team. Knock it off.
Right.
Prepare for...
A search and rescue of our spy. Soh-Larr.
The Skrulls have invaded
yet another border planet.
This time. Torfa.
Soh-Larr sent us a warning signal.
It was intercepted.
and his cover's blown.
The Skrull general Talos has
sent kill units to find him.
Should they reach
him before we do.
the intelligence he's acquired over
three years is as good as theirs.
The Accusers will bomb a Skrull
stronghold here in the south.
We slip in. we locate
Soh-Larr. and we get out.
Leaving them none the wiser.
The Torfan populace. we are
not to interfere with them.
nor them with us. Nothing compromises
the security of our mission.
Proceed with caution.
Follow protocol before
extracting him.
This is a dangerous mission.
We must all be ready to
join the Collective...
if that is our fate today.
- For the good of all Kree.
- For the good of all Kree!
Vers. track Soh-Larr's beacon.
Att-Lass. Minn-Erva. find elevation.
Locals on the periphery.
- Maybe a dozen.
- Minn-Erva?
Do you read me? Anybody copy?
His beacon's coming from that temple.
Let's move.
No. This is a perfect
spot for an ambush.
- Only one way in and one way out.
- We can get past the locals.
We don't know if they are locals.
Too risky.
You don't have to go with me.
I'll go alone.
No. you won't.
Right. We keep a close radius.
We lose comms. we
meet back in here.
Come on.
- Att-Lass. you getting this?
- Copy. I see them.
Minn-Erva. do you
have eyes on us?
- Keep them back. Minn-Erva?
- Does anybody copy?
I don't wanna hurt you.
Keep back!
Stand back!
They're locals. I found two dead. No green.
They're just starving.
- HGX-78.
- 2RT-79. 8XX.
Get back.
Skrulls!
Vers!
Vers... it's an ambush...
Incoming!
Talk to me. Do you copy?
How did you know the code?
How about I tell you my secret...
...when you tell me yours.
Let's open her up.
- Where are we?
- Standby.
Where's your head at?
In the clouds. Where's yours?
On my shoulders.
About to show these boys how we do it.
You ready?
- Higher. further. faster. baby.
- That's right.
This can't be right.
Go back even further.
You're too fast! You
need to go slow!
Now who is this person?
Are--- are we in the right...
What the hell are you thinking?
You don't belong out here!
I think we went back too far.
You won't let me drive.
Let me try it back.
What the hell is wrong with her?
You'll kill yourself.
They'll never let you fly.
I am not the only one
who's confused here.
You're a decent pilot. but
you're too emotional.
You do know why they call
it a "cockpit". don't you?
...Huge rubble.
throughout the cosmos...
...shift the moon and the sun
and the stars in the sky.
And soon. they'll wile away.
Flew out throughout the night.
Did you see it?
Get your butts inside. it's time to eat.
Prepare for take-off. Lt. Trouble.
Charming memory.
Hang on. I think I got it.
Goose likes you.
She doesn't typically
take to people.
- Early start to your morning?
- Late night. actually.
I can't sleep when there's work to do.
Sound familiar?
Flying airplanes never
feels like work.
- Wonderful view. isn't it?
- I prefer the view from up there.
You'll get there
soon enough. ace.
Wait. wait. wait. that's her.
- Get her back.
- Standby.
...sound familiar...
Wonderful view. isn't it?
- I prefer the view from up there.
- You'll get there soon enough...
What's that on her shirt?
I couldn't read it.
Wonderful view. isn't it?
- I prefer the view from up there.
- You'll get there soon enough...
Focus... Look down.
Focus.
Pegasus... Dr. Wendy Lawson.
That's her.
- Do you hear that. too?
- Now track the location.
Got it.
Now track Lawson until we
find the energy signature.
Interesting.
Hold on...
- Go back right before this.
- Okay.
Now let's see where
you're headed.
That's right. Look at the
coordinates... Focus.
That's it. That's it.
Almost there...
You're almost there. Don't fight it.
Focus! Focus!
Get her back! Get her back now.
Do we have any information
we can act on?
Just that Lawson was
somewhere on planet C-53.
We're on our way.
Then dig. dig. dig. deeper.
Lawson is our link to
that lightspeed engine.
And everything we're after.
That did something.
Try that again?
Not yet!
What did you do to me?
We're just after little information.
- What did you put in my head?
- Nothing that wasn't already there.
But those aren't my memories.
Yeah. it's like a
bad trip in there.
I'm not surprised you
can't keep it straight.
They really did a number on you.
Enough of your mindgames.
What do you want?
We're looking for the location of a Dr.
Lawson and her lightspeed engine.
I don't know any Dr. Lawson.
Then why is she in your head?
Either of you wouldn't happen to know
how these things come off. would you?
No? Fine.
Hey.
You do know why
they call it co...
Leaving so soon?
We just got to know each other.
Vers to Starforce Command.
Do you read me?
Hello?
Do you copy?
Hi. I'm Vers. Kree Starforce.
Is this C-53?
Do you understand me? Is my
universal translator working?
Yeah. I understand you.
Good. Are you in charge of
security for this district?
Sort of.... The movie
theater has its own guy.
Where can I find
communication equipment?
Thank you.
Track the pod and find the girl.
She knows more than she knows.
Hey!
This one's taken.
Come on...
Vers...
- Clarify: CQC-39.
- GRX8-1600.
And I'm fine. thank
you for asking.
- Is everyone okay? What happened?
- Skrull ambush.
I thought we'd lost you.
- Did you find Soh-Larr?
- It wasn't Soh-Larr.
Talos simmed him. Even knew his code.
That's impossible.
That code was buried
in his unconscious.
The Skrulls messed with my mind.
The machine that they used.
I think it's how they
extracted Soh-Larr's code.
- Vers. where are you?
- I'm on Planet C-53.
The Skrulls are looking
for someone named Lawson.
Who?
She's who I see...
She's what?
Vers.
Vers. what?
She's a scientist.
They think that she's cracked
the code on lightspeed tech.
I have to get to her before they do or
else they'll be able to invade galaxies.
No. You've been
caught once already.
How far is C-53?
Closest jump point is 22 hours.
Vers. hold your position
until we get there.
Keep your comms online
so we can contact...
No. What if they get
a hold of it before...
Vers.
Vers!
If the Skrulls got to her.
she's compromised.
She's stronger than you think.
Ever been to C-53?
Once.
It's a real shithole.
You called this in?
Beacon activated.
Excuse me. Miss.
Did you know anything
about a lady blowing a hole
through the roof of that
Blockbuster over there?
Witness says she looks
dressed for laser tag.
Yeah. I think she went that way.
Uhh. I'd like to ask
you some questions.
Maybe give you the 411 on
the late-night drive-bys.
How do we know...
you're not one of
those shapeshifters?
Congratulations. Agent Fury. You have
finally asked a relevant question.
No. Congratulations to you.
Starforce lady!
You're under arrest.
Rook!
Rook! Let's roll!
- Did you see her weapon?
- I did not.
Suspect on northbound train.
In pursuit.
"Trust me. true believer.
Trust me..."
"Trust me. true believer..."
Train's headed to
a tunnel up ahead.
Let's greet them at the station.
Agent Fury. this is Agent Coulson.
Umm..
Uh. I'm still here at the
Blockbuster. and uh...
Where'd everybody go? I
finished collecting evidence...
Official SHIELD activity.
Stay back.
Nice scuba suit.
Lighten up. honey. huh?
Gonna smile for me?
All life on Earth is carbon-based.
Not this guy.
Whatever he runs on. it's not
on the periodic table.
So you're saying he's
not from around here?
Hey. how's your eye?
Well. I'd say fine.
But it can't believe
what it's seeing.
You said...
this thing looked like Coulson?
Mmm. Talked like him. too.
And the woman said
that there were more?
The word she used
was infiltration.
- You believe her?
- Not til I saw this.
What's your plan?
I'll find the Blockbuster girl.
I got word on a motorcycle thief
that fits her description.
If she can tell us why
these lizards are here...
Maybe she can tell us how
to kick 'em to the curb.
Good.
Do it alone. though.
You can't trust anyone.
- Not even our own men.
- Yes. sir.
Wow. They're ugly
bastards. aren't they?
Yeah. well.
He's no Brad Pitt. sir.
Safe journey to the beyond. my friend.
I will finish what we started.
I wouldn't get too
close there. boss.
No one in or out.
- What can I get you?
- Where was this photograph taken?
- Airport?
- Where's Pegasus?
That's classified. Not unlike
the file I've started on you.
I see you've changed
it up a bit since then.
Grunge is a good look for you.
- Did you have a rough day. Agent Fury?
- It's cool.
You know. had a space
invasion. big car chase...
Got to watch an alien autopsy...
- Typical 9 to 5.
- So you saw one.
I was never one to
believe in aliens...
...but I can't unsee that.
This is gonna get a little
awkward. but I gotta ask...
You think I'm one of
those green things.
Can't be too careful.
You. are looking at 100 %
red-blooded Earthman.
I'm afraid I'm gonna need proof.
- We talking cheek swab or urine sample?
- No. The DNA would match.
Want my AOL password?
Skrulls can only sim recent
memories of their hosts' bodies.
You wanna get personal.
- Where were you born?
- Huntsville. Alabama.
But technically I don't
remember that part.
- Name of your first pet?
- Mr. Snoofers.
- Mr. Snoofers?
- That's what I said. Do I pass?
- Not yet. First job?
- Soldier. Straight outta high school.
Left the ranks a full-bird colonel.
- Then?
- Spy.
- Where?
- It's the Cold War. We were everywhere.
Belfast. Bucharest.
Belgrade. Budapest.
I like the B's. I
can make 'em rhyme.
Now?
Been riding a desk for the
past six years trying to
figure out where our future
enemies are coming from.
Never occured to me they
would be coming from above.
Name a detail so bizarre.
a Skrull could never fabricate it.
If toast is cut
diagonally. I can't eat it.
You didn't need that. did you?
No. No. I didn't.
But I enjoyed it.
Okay. Your turn. Prove
you're not a Skrull.
And how is that suppposed to
prove to me you're not a Skrull?
That's a photon blast.
- And?
- A Skrull can't do that.
So. a full-bird colonel turned
spy turned SHIELD Agent.
Must have pretty high
security clearance.
Where's Pegasus?
Okay. The Skrulls sim alien races to
infiltrate and take over planets...
and you're a Kree.
- A race of noble warriors.
- Heroes.
Noble warrior heroes.
So. what do Skrulls want
with Dr. Lawson?
They believe that she developed
a lightspeed engine at Pegasus.
Lightspeed engine?
Gotta admit. that's not the
craziest thing I've heard today.
Well. it's still early.
And you? What do you want?
To stop the Skrulls before
they become unstoppable.
And?
Look. war is a universal language.
I know a rogue soldier
when I see one.
You got a personal
stake in this.
This is government property.
Turn your vehicle around.
Nicholas Joseph Fury.
Agent of SHIELD.
Place your thumb on the pad.
One moment.
Nicholas Joseph Fury?
You have three names?
Everybody calls me Fury.
Not Nicholas. not Joseph. not Nick.
Just Fury.
- What does your Mom call you?
- Fury.
- What do you call her?
- What about your kids?
- If I had them...
- they'll call me Fury.
- You're cleared for access.
Thank you.
Oh. hold up.
You look like somebody's
disaffected niece.
Put that on.
- What is it?
- It's the SHIELD logo.
Does announcing your identity on clothing
help with the covert part of your job?
Said the space soldier who
was wearing a rubber suit.
Lose the flannel.
How can I help you?
We're Agents of SHIELD.
We're looking for a
woman named Lawson.
Dr. Wendy Lawson.
Do you know her?
Follow me.
You familiar with the
phrase 'welcome wagon'?
No.
Well this ain't it.
- Is that a communicator?
- Yeah.
State-of-the-art two-way pager.
- Who are you paging?
- My Mom. Don't worry.
I didn't mention you.
DETAINED WITH TARGET. NEED BACKUP
After you.
Impressive.
You should see what I can
do with a paperclip.
Hey. how are you. huh?
Look at you. Just look at you!
Aren't you the cutest little thing?
Aren't you cute?
What's your name. huh?
What's your name? "Goose".
Cool name for a cool cat.
Fury?
I'll be back.
Hold up. Lemme get my fingerprint out.
Just let me unravel this...
You sat there. and watched me play with
tape. when all you had to do was...
I didn't want to
steal your thunder.
Lawson.
Lawson's plan for the
lightspeed engine.
I wonder why they
terminated the project.
Maybe because she's.... coo-coo.
- Kree glyphs?
- Huh?
Lawson is not coo-coo.
She's Kree.
- Well... she's dead.
- What?
She crashed an Aces aircraft during
an unauthorized test flight.
Took a pilot down with her.
That's why security
here's so friendly.
They're covering up a
billion-dollar mistake.
Oh. And your lightspeed engine?
It's toast.
- When did this crash happen?
- Six years ago. 1989.
Who was the pilot?
Most of this thing's
redacted. but...
there is a testimonial here from a Maria
Rambeau. Last person to see them alive.
Back in a few.
This isn't about fighting wars.
It's about ending them.
I know Lawson was Kree.
She was here on C-53 and
died in a plane crash.
Do you know anything about this?
I just discovered a mission
report sent from C-53.
There's only so much I'm
cleared to tell you. Vers.
But...
Lawson. was an undercover Kree
operative named Mar-Vell.
She was working on a
unique energy core...
Experimenting with tech that apparently.
could help us win the war.
She still here?
She's cooperating with
the investigation. sir.
- You men. stay here.
- Yes. sir.
I want to question her alone.
Excellent work. Nicholas.
Does it say anything about me?
Anything about you?
No. of course. not.
Why would it?
I found evidence that I...
had a life here.
On C-53?
Mar-Vell is who I see when I visit the
Supreme Intelligence. I knew her.
And I knew her as Lawson.
This sounds like Skrull
simulation. Vers.
No. it's not because I remember.
I was here...
Stop. Remember your training.
Know your enemy.
It could be you.
Do not let your emotions
override your judgment.
She's on sub-level 6.
I'll get off on 5. hit
the stairs in case she
makes a run for it.
Do a pincer move. Like
we did in Havana.
Right. Like we did in Havana.
We're nearing the jump point. Leave
your beacon on so I can find you.
We'll get to the
bottom of this. Vers.
Together.
Okay.
Vers!
Fury's colluding with the target.
Then why would he call us in?
All I know is we take him in. too.
Dead or alive.
Dead or alive?
Go! Go. go!
Was it something I said?
Now. you know. I don't
really need these to see.
But...
They do kinda complete the look.
Don't you think?
- You called it in?
- My bad!
- Coulson! You have eyes on them?
- They're not down here.
Let's try up there.
What?
Your communicator. You obviously
can't be trusted with it.
Do you know how to
fly this thing?
Uhh. we'll see.
That's a 'yes or no' question.
Yes.
That's what I'm talking about.
We got a stowaway.
Hang on. Goose.
Goose.
Who's a good kitty. huh? Huh. Goose?
Yes. that's right. Who's
a good kitty. Goose?
- You the good kitty.
- See anyone you know?
Funny story...
I arrived on Hala.
near dead. no memory...
That was six years ago.
So you think. you're the pilot
that went down with Dr. Lawson?
I'm saying the last person to see
them alive could probably tell us.
- Maria Rambeau.
- So how do we get to Louisiana?
Due east. Hang a
right at Memphis.
That agent...
That stopped the Skrulls
from finding us...
Coulson. The new guy.
- I guess he doesn't hate me yet.
- Yeah. well. Give him time.
I guess he had a
feeling. you know.
Went with his gut against orders.
It's a really hard thing to do.
That's what keeps us human.
I get in trouble for that.
A lot.
I see that about you.
Rescuing the guy who sold
you out to the Skrulls?
I'm guessing that's not standard
Kree operating procedure.
Well. I won't tell your boss
if you don't tell mine.
Ronan.
The Accusers completed
their operation. but the
greater mission was a failure
thanks to your team.
It was a trap.
To lure our operative Vers
to talk for her kidnapper.
Give us the location. We'll take
care of the terrorist threat.
By bombing them out of the galaxy.
No.
- We'll handle this.
- Several Skrulls anywhere...
is a threat to Kree everywhere.
Where are they?
- They are...
- Lost.
They are lost. for now.
But we will find them.
Do so.
Or we will.
Maintain the course for C-53.
Excuse me. I'm looking
for Maria Rambeau?
Auntie Carol?
Mom. it's Auntie Carol!
I knew it! Everyone
said you were dead.
But we knew they were lying.
I'm not really who
you think I am.
- That is the craziest shit I ever heard.
- Green. transforming aliens?
- There's no such thing.
- You're absolutely right. young lady.
There is no such thing.
'Cause if there were...
We would wanna keep
that to ourselves.
You don't believe me?
No way. That's so cool.
She can do a lot more than
make tea with those hands.
- Like what? Show us.
- Maybe later.
I kept all your stuff.
I'll go get it.
You wanna give her
a hand with that?
You don't remember anything?
I can see...
...flashes...
Little moments.
But I can't tell what's real.
If I could just piece together
what happened that morning...
Maybe it'll make sense.
You woke me up. banging
on my door at dawn.
Your usual move.
Back then we had to
get up so early.
The Air Force still wasn't
letting women fly combat. so...
testing Lawson's plane was our only
shot at doing something that mattered.
And you wanted to race to the
base. in your old Mustang.
and I wasn't about to argue. 'cause
I knew my Camaro would dominate.
But you cheated.
Took a shortcut.
Since when is a
shortcut cheating?
Since it violates the predetermined
rules of engagement.
- I definitely don't remember those.
- Of course. you don't.
When I got to the hangar...
Lawson was agitated.
She said she had lives to save.
She was trying to take the
Aces up herself. but you said...
"If there were lives at stake...
I would fly the plane."
Yup. Big hero moment.
The kind of moment we've
both been waiting for.
The Doc was always unique.
That's why I liked her. but...
Now you're saying she's...
from another planet.
- I know this must be hard for you.
- What. this part right here?
No.
No. Mmm-mm.
Know what's hard?
It is losing my best friend
in a mission so secret. they
act like it never even happened.
Hard...
is knowing you were out there
somewhere. too damn stubborn to die.
And now you come up in
here after 6 years...
With your super-charged fire-hands
and you expect me to call you...
I don't even know what... "Vers"?
Is that really who you are now?
I don't know.
Come look.
This is me and you on Halloween.
I'm Amelia Earhart. and
you're Janis Joplin.
This is you when you were little.
You didn't get along with your parents.
so Mom said we became your real family.
This is us on Christmas.
I got more...
Here's another picture of
you when you were little.
And this is how you
actually graduated...
Oh. wait. I forgot. your jacket.
Mom doesn't let me wear it anymore
after I spilled ketchup on it.
That was all that
survived the crash.
Or so we thought.
Don't answer that.
It's just my neighbor.
They can change into anyone.
Hi. there.
What do you want?
Hey. Tom. This is
my friend. Carol.
Pleased to meet you!
Yow!
Static electricity
out here's no joke.
I noticed that peculiar bird
you got parked by the road.
and I was just wondering
if you'd mind if I
bring the boys over to
get a closer looksie?
- A closer looksie?
- Yeah.
To see the bird parked
out by the road.
You're really working overtime
to sell this one. aren't you...
Talos?
I'm sorry. Tom. This
isn't a good time.
I'll come by tomorrow? Okay?
You know. you really should
be kinder to your neighbors.
You never know when you're gonna
need to borrow some sugar.
Hang on a second.
Before you go swinging
those jazz-hands around.
making a mess in
your friend's house.
- and... it's a lovely home.
- Oh. my God...
What the hell?!
No one's gonna hurt the girl.
Just. don't kill me.
It would really complicate
the situation.
I'm about 5 seconds from complicating that
wall with some ugly-ass Skrull brains.
I'm sorry I simmed your boss. But now
I stand before you as my true self.
- Without deception.
- And who's that out there?
Okay. That's a fair point.
But I'm sure that
you understand.
I had to take some precautions.
I saw you crush
20 of my best men
with your hands bound.
I just wanna talk.
The last time we talked. I ended
up hanging from my ankles.
That was before I
knew who you were.
Before I knew what made you
different from the others.
I have an audio
recording from Pegasus.
of your voice. from a
plane crash. six years ago.
On a device I believe
you call a "black box".
They told me it was destroyed in the crash.
How'd you get it?
Does she not understand? Young lady
I have a special skill that kinda
allows me to get into places
I'm not supposed to be in.
Call me young lady again. and I'm gonna put
my foot in a place it's not supposed to be.
Am I supposed to
guess. where that is?
- Your ass.
Okay. I get it. We're all
a little on edge here.
But look. I just need your help
decoding some coordinates.
If you sit down. you
listen to this.
I assure you. it'll
be worth your while.
Call your buddy back
inside and I'll listen.
Deal.
Oh. my God!
Get that thing away!
How'd that get in here?
The cat? This isn't what
you're afraid of. is it?
That's not a cat.
That's a Flerken.
- A Flerken?
- Mom?
- Monica...
- Why can't I listen too?
What's happening?
It's loading.
Punch in the coordinates:
5229. -47. 8.768. 0.2.
Copy that. Where
are we going. Doc?
- My laboratory.
- Your laboratory?
- What do you mean?
- Oh. no.
Is that... Wait. what is that?
It's not showing up on my radar.
Go. Carol. Fly!
That's no MIG. Lawson.
- Who the hell are they?
- Those are the bad guys.
- Fly faster. now.
- Yes. ma'am.
- What do they want?
- Me. My work.
I never should have
brought you along.
Here comes some G's.
They're firing backwards.
Hold on!
Bail out! Bail out! Bail out!
Stay with me. Lawson!
Danvers. do you copy?
Yeah. I copy. On the ground.
- Can anyone hear me?
- Yeah. I copy.
Doc?
Your blood...
it's blue.
Never mind that.
How's my hair?
Help me out. will you?
- I have to destroy it before they get here.
- What? Lawson?
You remember what I said about
our work here? What it's for?
- To end wars?
- Yeah.
But the wars are
bigger than you know.
Damn it!
My name is not Lawson.
My real name. is Mar-Vell...
We have no interest
in hurting you.
No?!
Because all the shooting kinda
gave me the wrong impression!
The energy core...
Where is it?
Pararescue's on the way.
You have two minutes
until you're surrounded.
Then I see no reason to
prolong this conversation.
No. wait!
You mean that energy core?
Commander. She's still moving.
- Permission to fire.
- Hold your fire.
There's nothing left.
The core has been destroyed.
"VERS"
She absorbed its' power.
She's coming with us.
He lied to me.
- Everything that I knew was a lie.
- Now...
- ...you understand.
- What?
What do I understand now?
Yon-Rogg killed Mar-Vell.
He killed her.
Because she found out that
she was on the wrong side
of an unjust war.
No. Your people
are terrorists...
that kill innocents. I
saw the ruins on Torfa.
Ruins that the Accusers
are responsible for.
My people lived as
refugees. on Torfa.
Homeless. ever since
we resisted Kree rule.
and they destroyed our planet.
Now the handful of
us that are left.
will be slaughtered next.
Unless. you will help me
finish what Mar-Vell started.
The coordinates you
found. would've powered
a lightspeed ship capable of
carrying us to safety. A new home.
Where the Kree can't reach us.
Lawson always told us that her work
at Pegasus wasn't to fight wars...
But to end them.
She wanted you to help
us find the core.
Well. I already destroyed it.
No. you destroyed the engine. The core
that powered it is in a remote location.
If you help us decode
those coordinates...
We can find it.
You'll use it to destroy us.
We just want a home.
You and I lost everything
at the hands of the Kree.
Can't you see it now?
You're not one of them.
You don't know me.
You have no idea who I am.
I don't even know who I am.
You are Carol Danvers.
You are the woman on that
black box risking her life
to do the right thing.
My best friend...
who supported me as a mother.
and a pilot when
no one else did.
You're smart. and funny. and
a huge pain in the ass.
And you are the most
powerful person I knew.
Way before you could shoot
fire from your fist.
Do you hear me?
I know I don't deserve
your trust. but...
you were our only lead.
We discovered that
your energy signature
matched Mar-Vell's core.
Now. we know why.
If only you knew. the
importance of it to me.
I just need your help
decoding the coordinates
to Mar-Vell's lab.
Those weren't coordinates.
They're safe vectors.
Orbital positioning and velocity.
You didn't find her lab on Earth.
because it's not on Earth.
That was the location on the day
of the crash six years ago.
If we track its course. we'll
find it. in orbit. right now.
It's just basic physics.
In orbit?
Was that so difficult to figure out?
I mean. you're my science guy. right?
Yon-Rogg will catch
up to us soon.
We've got to get to the
core before he does.
You're going to space?
In what?
A few tweaks to your
vessel should do it.
I can handle the modifications.
Hmm. Your science guy.
Well. I could use a co-pilot.
No. No. I... I can't.
- I can't leave Monica.
- Why?
It's okay. I can stay
with grandma and poppop.
There's no way I'm going baby.
It's too dangerous.
Testing for new aerospace tech is
dangerous. Didn't you used to do that?
Your plan is to leave the atmosphere in
a craft not designed for the journey.
and you anticipate hostile encounters with
a technologically superior foreign enemy.
Correct?
- That's what I'm saying. You have to go.
- Monica...
You will just fly the coolest
mission in the history of missions.
And you're gonna give it up to sit on the
couch and watch Fresh Prince with me?
I just think you should
consider what kind of
example you're setting
for your daughter.
Your Mom's lucky.
When they were handing out kids.
they gave her the toughest one.
Lieutenant Trouble.
You remember.
Is that mine?
Oh. no.
You hang on to it
until I come back.
But there is something that
I need your help with.
I can't wear these
Kree colors anymore.
And since you're obviously the only person
around here with any sense of style...
Whoa.
No.
Uh-uhh.
Definitely not.
Well. since we're
on the same team...
How do I look?
Fresh.
What took you so long?
I'm fine. thanks for asking.
- PRY46--
- Enough with codes.
The system is fallible
as we've learned.
Okay. Then let's do this.
Who do I see. when I commune
with the Supreme Intelligence?
A person you most admire
and respect. I guess.
But you would never tell me who.
And what is your
earliest memory of Hala?
A transfusion.
Blue blood running
through my veins.
Whose blood?
That's my blood.
that's coursing
through her veins.
- What have you done to her?
- You're too late.
She knows?
Ronan. Skrulls have infiltrated C-53.
Come at once.
For the good of all
Kree. Commander.
The infestation
will be eradicated.
Passing 500 and climbing.
You know. you really shouldn't
have that thing on your lap.
My alliance with you.
it's tenuous at best.
But as long as he continues
to freak you out...
Can I ask you something?
You just turn into
anything you want?
- Well. I have to see it first.
- Can you all do it?
Physiologically. yeah. But...
It takes practice. and dare I
say it. talent to do what...
Can you turn into a cat?
What's a cat?
What about a filing cabinet?
Why would I turn into
a filing cabinet...?
A venus fly trap. I'll give you $50 right
now if you turn into a venus fly trap.
Switching engines from scramjet
to fusion. Buckle up. folks.
- Is this normal. like space turbulence?
- Pretty much.
Locking in a coordinate grid.
Where is it?
It's here. It's gotta be here.
Well. is it in front....
of all that nothing. or behind it?
Decloaking activated.
Is that it? The core?
In her notes. she called
it the Tesseract.
What was Lawson doing
with all this kid stuff?
We're not alone.
Talos!
He didn't come here
for the Tesseract.
We didn't know what to do.
Mar-Vell warned us not to
send a signal for any reason.
- Or the Kree would find us.
- You did the right thing.
It's okay. It's okay.
She's alright. She's a friend.
I am not gonna hurt you.
She led me to you.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't know.
Carol...
this is war.
My hands are filthy
from it. too.
But we're here now.
You found my family.
This is just the beginning. There's
thousands of us separated from each other.
Scattered throughout the galaxy.
If I played the same pinball machine for
6 years. I'd have some high scores. too.
Fraternizing with the enemy.
Uh-uh.
What did you do to your uniform?
They got in her head.
Just like we thought.
The Supreme Intelligence
will set her straight.
You can see they're not soldiers.
Let them go.
- You can have me.
- And the core?
You lied to me.
I made you a better
version of yourself.
What's given can be taken away.
There she is.
Seems like your time on C-53
jogged the old memory.
This jacket? It's
killer. by the way.
The music. it's a nice touch.
- Let... me... out.
- No can do.
If you hurt them. I will
burn you to the ground.
With what. exactly?
- Your power comes from us.
- You didn't give me these powers.
The blast did.
And yet. you've never had the
strength to control them on your own.
Species: Flerken. Threat: High.
It's a cat. Not Hannibal Lecter.
Species: Human male.
Threat: Low to none.
That thing is clearly busted.
Load the Flerken on the heli.
Eject the others into space.
You did good. ace.
Thanks to you. those insidious shapeshifters
will threaten our borders no more.
I used to believe your lies. But the
Skrulls are just fighting for a home.
You're talking about destroying them
because they won't submit to your rule.
And neither will I.
We found you.
- We embraced you as our own.
- You stole me.
From my home.
My family. my friends.
It's cute how hard you try.
Remember...
Without us...
Give it up. Carol!
...you're weak.
You're flawed.
Helpless.
We saved you.
Without us...
you're only human.
You're right.
I'm only human.
On Hala. you were reborn.
Vers.
My name... is Carol.
She's trying to break out.
I've been fighting with one
arm tied behind my back.
But what happens when...
...I'm finally set free?
You. know you're glowing. right?
I'll explain it later.
Take the Tesseract.
Leave the lunchbox.
- Me?
- Yes.
- I'm not touching that thing.
- Want me to get you an oven mitt?
Get the Skrulls in the
QuadJet and go.
Take the Flerken with you.
- What about you?
- I'll buy you some time.
I'm picking you up now.
I'm trusting you not to eat me.
Hey. guys.
Arm-wrestle for the Tesseract?
I used to find you amusing.
Let's put an end to this!
Okay!
Good kitty!
You knew all along.
Is that why we never hung out?
No. I just never liked you.
Hey! In a hurry?
- Don't make me do this.
- Okay.
Now! Come on! Do your thing.
Come on!
Dammit. Goose. Pick a side.
Take them to the hangar too.
We'll blast them all into space.
Play it cool.
Just like Havana.
- Do you have the thing?
- The Flerken kitty ate it.
Come on. Move. Move!
Follow my lead.
Cover her eyes.
Get on the ship.
Let's go. let's go.
Nice diversion.
I could've swore.
I put it in there.
- Minn-Erva. take them down in a dropship.
- On it.
You all right. friend?
Never... better.
We've got a bogey.
Coming in hot.
Yes!
What the hell was that?
Deploy ballistic warheads.
That's impossible.
C-53 doesn't have a defense system
advanced enough to destroy our warheads.
That's not their
defense system. Ronan.
Take her down.
Return to the jump point.
We'll be back for the weapon.
The core?
The woman.
I'm so proud of you.
You've come a long way since I
found you that day by the lake.
But can you keep your emotions in
check long enough to take me on?
Or will it get the better
of you. as always?
I always told you...
you'll be ready. the day you can
knock me down as yourself.
This is that moment.
This is that moment. Vers!
Turn off the light show.
and prove. prove to me.
you can beat me with...
I have nothing to prove to you.
Destination: Hala.
- I can't go back empty-handed.
- You won't be empty-handed.
I'm sending you with a message.
Tell the Supreme Intelligence
that I'm coming to end it.
The war. the lies. all of it.
You can't do this.
That was a close call. huh. Goosey?
Huh?
The bad guy's still in
there somewhere--- Oh!
Mother Flerken!
- You okay?
- Yeah. It's just a scratch.
No...
I can't believe you got into
the raddest dogfight ever.
I'd say you arrived
just in time.
That's some nifty flying
you did out there.
SHIELD could always
use a good pilot like you.
I'll consider it.
As long as you don't call
my flying nifty again.
How's your eye?
Getting better every second.
Just so I'm clear. you were
Soh-Larr. and the SHIELD agent?
Keller.
Tied my boss up.
stole his identity.
I borrowed his likeness.
I'm no thief.
It's a little like thief.
Whose side are you on?
You're good to go here til you recover. but
you and your family will need a new look.
- I could go back to being your boss.
- Please don't.
Come on. I love sporting
his beautiful blue eyes.
No way. you guys have the best eyes.
Don't ever change your eyes.
I'll help you find a home.
Finish what Mar-Vell started.
They can stay here
with us. can't they. Mom?
They won't be safe here. baby.
Auntie Carol is right.
They need their own home.
I'll be back before you know it.
Maybe I can fly up and
meet you halfway.
Only if you learn to glow.
like your Auntie Carol.
Or maybe I'll build a spaceship.
You don't know.
He doesn't.
Keep the Tesseract on Earth.
Hidden.
You're sure that's what
Marvel would want?
- Mar-Vell.
- That's what I said.
It's two words. Mar-Vell.
Mar-Vell.
Marvel sounds a lot better.
You know. like the Marvelettes?
Not ringing any bells?
Keep singing. Maybe
it'll come back to me.
I upgraded it.
Range should be. a couple
galaxies. at least.
What? You think I'm
gonna crank call you?
For emergencies only. Okay?
Well. if you're ever
passing back through this
galaxy. be sure to give
a brother a shout.
We got the ketchup stain off.
Thanks. Lt. Trouble.
It's hard for me to
say goodbye. too.
Go on.
Glad to have you back. sir.
This came for you.
So. is it true?
That the Kree burned your eye out because
you refused to give them the Tesseract?
I'll neither confirm nor deny
the facts of that story.
Understood.
I'm sorry to report that we still
haven't found the Tesseract.
I'm sure it will
turn up somewhere.
I'll let you know when it does.
Then what?
Sir?
We have no idea what other
intergalactic threats are out there.
And our one-woman security
force had a prior
commitment on the other
side of the universe.
SHIELD alone can't protect us.
We need to find more.
- More weapons?
- More heroes.
You think we can find
others like her?
We found her and we
weren't even looking.
Get some rest. sir.
You got a big decision to make.
Subbed by: Fuji69Film and darelik
corrections by dreg05